we have a special guest star in this
episode Scott that's it both you and
Scott have appeared in two episodes of
the TV show monk Tony shaloo was the
nicest he was throwing something to try
to get in the trash can and when it hit
the trash can it made like a ping and I
started laughing and then the two of us
sat there and did our impressions of the
noises of things going in the trash can
like
like we were such dorks and we cracked
up I don't know he he's just so fun I
just adored
[Music]
him this episode was filmed during May
2006 and so Angela my question for both
of us is what were you doing flash back
now to May 2006 and what were you up to
well I had a journal entry
from May 3rd 2006 this is what I wrote I
wrote that I was doing a photo shoot
with my cat Lucy for cat fancy magazine
Angela Kinsey what shut the front door
right now what do you know what I wrote
in my journal no for this week of May of
2006 I did a photo shoot with my cat
Andy for People magazine I'm not joking
lady lady how did we not know that we
did photo shoots with our cats at the
same time oh my gosh first of all this
is why we're BFFs all right this is why
our life has very strange ways that it
is parallel so was Lucy on the cover of
cat Fancy no Lucy was not on the cover
because she was a rescue she was not a
purebred cat but also Jenna cat fancy
doesn't let humans on the cover so
that's like it's only hats on the cover
okay but the cool thing was is that Lucy
and I got like I think I I mean I saved
the magazine I think we got like four
pages so Lucy and I are in the center I
guess we're the center fold oh you are
the center fold of cat fancy magazine so
Lucy and I look amazing it they're some
of the best pictures I feel like I have
how was she during the photo shoot well
yeah I should probably give you some
backstory about Lucy Lucy loved to sleep
oh so uh Lucy did nothing Lucy just laid
there and I mean Lucy is I love her she
rip Lucy she had a great long life but
she um really just loved to Lounge she
was a lounger so I in many shots I'm
just laying next to her cuz that's like
her favorite thing to
do but what about you what was your
People magazine shoot like with Andy
okay well Andy was also a rescue but he
was a semif feral cat I had found him he
was eating out of a dumpster back in
bville Missouri where I went to college
I think he was about like 5 or 6 months
old when I got him and he was just
always a little we said he was always a
little wild and he loved me and he
snuggled me and he was so gentle and
sweet but he didn't love strangers in
the house and so when the People
magazine guys came over not only were
they all there kind of causing a ruckus
you know and Andy was a little bit like
I'm out of here they wanted to do the
photo shoot out side and they wanted me
to hold him forget it mine was inside oh
oh my gosh angel I'm in like full hair
and makeup with this dress on they were
like okay we're ready for you will you
come out with Andy so I'm holding Andy
and I think if you look in the photo you
can see that he and I are both a little
tense but I'm smiling super big as if
I'm not tense and I wrote in my journal
Angela I wrote in my Journal that he
clawed my stomach and I had like like
bloody claw marks in my stomach from the
photo shoot because he wanted to get
away a lady I I do remember like calling
my mom and I was so excited cuz I hadn't
really been in any magazines ever
obviously in my whole life and I was
like Mom I'm going to be in cat fancy
and my mom was like
what I was like me and Lucy mom anyway
that is so cute I love that now I really
want to see I remember you doing that
but now I need to see the picture okay
well I have a ton of makeup on just a
ton of makeup and I'm smiling in a
really weird maniacal way and um I
called my mom after that photo shoot
Angela and my mom was so sweet she was
like oh I am just so proud of you both
just so proud of you both she's like
just think about that little kitten that
you found in that dumpster in Kirksville
Missouri he drove all the way to Los
Angeles with you onto the pages of
People magazine what a life you've given
him that is that is so adorable that is
such a mom moment oh my Lord I
[Music]
know why does Jim do his Talking Heads
in front of the outside facing window
while everyone else's Talking Heads are
inside of the window that faces the
bullpen of the office no that is a great
catch it really is so I emailed Greg
Daniels and I asked him was this
deliberate was this an accident what
does he have to say and he said that it
was something that Randall Einhorn our
cinematographer suggested to Greg
starting with the pilot and Greg
absolutely loved it he said Randall's
intention here was that it didn't
necessarily have to be only Jim but the
idea was that any character that had a
future outside of Dunder Mifflin or held
some sort of internal optimism would sit
in front of a window leading out into
the world but characters who didn't want
to leave Dunder Mifflin or who maybe
were in more of a position of being
trapped would do their Talking Heads
facing into the office wow that's so
deep that's really deep yeah I'm I'm
sitting here racking my brain to think
if my character ever sat on that other
wall with the window facing out behind
her and the one that comes to my mind
and I think it might be the only one I'm
trying to think if there's any other one
it was when you and I did big prags
little prags yeah we did I think it's
the only time I ever sat there well for
a very long time I only sat there if I
was with Jim
wow which was really the only possible
future for Pam outside of the
office wow I that's so deep isn't that
crazy but otherwise she was rather
trapped in her you know bad decision of
being with Roy trapped or content you
know I mean some of us were just happy
with our lot in life yes um well that is
fascinating and I like it yeah I thought
that was a good one
Michael calls Dwight and Jim into the
conference room and he goes through a
list of Dwight's complaints and this is
my favorite part of the episode this is
it's so good and them made me laugh so
hard all right here are the list of
pranks that Jim has pulled on Dwight
that Dwight has reported ready okay yes
ready Jenna go number one number one he
replaced all of Dwight's pens and
pencils with crayons number two he had
everyone call him Dwayne all day which
by the way Jenna by the way guess who
would sometimes call him Dwayne who in a
scene who Oscar he did for real we for
real there were scenes where you'd be
like listen Dwayne I'd be like Dwight
it's Dwight and he'd be like ah crap
that is so funny somehow it went into
Oscar's brain in real life okay well Jim
also placed a bloody glove in Dwight's
desk drawer and tried to convince him
that he had committed murder yes uh
number four Jim told Dwight there was an
abandoned infant in the women's room he
went in to save the child and saw
Meredith on the can go the next one is
um that every time Dwight typed his name
it would just say diaper diapers yeah by
the end of the day Dwight complains that
his desk was moved 2 feet closer to The
copier and Jim admits that yes every
time Jim got up from his desk he moved
it a little closer to the cop here this
one is my favorite of all time of any
prank ever written about on the office
it's just a sentence we never see this
play out but my imagination of it is so
rich Dwight says he hit himself in the
head with his phone and Michael is like
what how could that have been Jim's
fault and then Jim in his talking head
to Jim yeah he and John's reaction
laughs he says that he put nickels in
Dwight's headset over the course of a
long time so that it got heavier and
heavier and then one day he took them
all out so that when Dwight answered the
phone it would be super light yeah I
just that's that is brilliant brilliant
that is brilliant Greg Daniels yeah
[Music]
clap e